<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PhotoGrid - Add fun to photo collages</title>
    <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PhotoGrid - Add fun to photo collages</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:02 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.photogrid.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create photo in photo edits | PhotoGrid Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_create_photo_in_photo_edits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_create_photo_in_photo_edits/</guid>
      <description> Choose a photo you’d like to create this photo in photo look. Select sticker and find “clip”. Clip the same photo. Copy the image and arrange each position.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to apply filters on your photo | PhotoGrid Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_apply_filters_on_your_photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 19:29:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_apply_filters_on_your_photo/</guid>
      <description>Crop, rotation, resize, blur and beautify your photos easily, you can even frame your images in Instagram&#39;s 1:1 aspect ratio!
Add stickers, texts, backgrounds, graffiti, boarders and pixelization, or adjust your photo&#39;s brightness, contrast, saturation and layout!
The latest smart facial recognition tech helps soften wrinkles, even out skin tones and remove blemishes instantly with a single tap.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add customized watermark | PhotoGrid Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_add_customized_watermark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:34:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_add_customized_watermark/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create snowing effect | PhotoGrid Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_create_snowing_effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:46:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/how_to_create_snowing_effect/</guid>
      <description> Apply a filter to lighten your photo. Find Shiny Bright sticker (it&#39;s free) and enlarge the snow sticker. Tap the sticker and use eraser to erase the snow on your face 😆.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clip - Crop some cool images from your photo library!</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/clip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:27:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/clip/</guid>
      <description>Cutout Tool lets you make &amp;amp; share custom stickers for everyone to use.
Choose an image of your closest friend or the icon you like, then clip it into a sticker!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Logo - Make your own style</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/custom-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:22:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/custom-logo/</guid>
      <description>You may want to remove watermark when you&#39;re editing your photo.
But in PhotoGrid, you can customize your own watermark and make your own special signature!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meme - Creating your Meme with GIF</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:19:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/meme/</guid>
      <description>See the video to see how to create a meme.
We provide trending photo and GIFs to let our user create the funniest meme in the world!
Also,You can move and resize the text boxes by dragging them around.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slide Show Maker - Share your best moments with your friends</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/slide-show-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:15:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/slide-show-maker/</guid>
      <description>Create slideshows with up to 50 images and add your favorite music, it&#39;s easy!
 Pick your photos and videos. Select your favorite filters and transitions. Choose the music from our gallery or your own songs and recordings. Save it to your camera roll and share it on Facebook, Instagram or Youtube.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrapbook - Personalize your photo in freestyle</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/scrapbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:10:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/scrapbook/</guid>
      <description> Scrapbook is very easy with simple user interface and can stitch a number of pics with multiple and creative frames, stickers, and backgrounds. You can make scrapbook collage with multiple photos and backgrounds, varieties frames, emojis, multiple stickers, a huge collection of fonts, creative Filters, and more.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Maker - Collage videos and photos</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/video-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 18:06:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/video-maker/</guid>
      <description> Best Instagram Video Editor and Photo Editor, add blur backgrounds with no cropping or watermarks! Add music and other effects on videos for Instagram. Merge and trim videos with effects. A professional photo editor with collage maker.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Face Filter - Real-time Selfie camera</title>
      <link>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/smart-face-filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:55:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.photogrid.app/posts/smart-face-filter/</guid>
      <description> Make ordinary photos look fantastic with 100+ animated filter effects. Whether you&#39;re on your own, with a friend, or with however many people there are, WowCam (AR Beauty Face filter) will preserve and add magic to your wonderful moments.    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>